<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on YenKha</title>
    <link>https://yenkha.com/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on YenKha</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright YenKha &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://yenkha.com/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://yenkha.com/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yenkha.com/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;transformational-leader-in-ai-ml--backend-platform-engineering&#34;&gt;Transformational Leader in AI, ML &amp;amp; Backend Platform Engineering&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a visionary data and software engineering leader, I drive technical innovation and strategic growth by architecting scalable data platforms, architectures, and pipelines that fuel AI/ML advancements. With expertise in software and backend engineering, I craft efficient, reliable, and future-proof solutions that accelerate AI-powered software product development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the forefront of AI exploration, I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about pushing the boundaries of Large Language Models (LLMs), language understanding, generation, and human-AI collaboration, empowering teams to pioneer groundbreaking AI innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;highly-driven-and-tenacious-technical-leader&#34;&gt;Highly driven and tenacious technical leader&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Results-driven technical leader with expertise in designing scalable data architectures, building efficient data pipelines, and developing large-scale AI/ML solutions using LLMs and NLP. Proficient in a range of technologies, including Go, Python, Spark, PostgreSQL, and Terraform, with experience in cloud and DevOps platforms such as AWS, Azure, GCP, Kubernetes, and Docker. Proven technical leadership skills, with a strong track record of team management and technical vision, and expertise in integrating APIs and systems using FastAPI, GraphQL, Kafka, and HuggingFace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;key-areas-of-expertise-include&#34;&gt;Key areas of expertise include:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Data Architecture: Designing scalable architectures for AI/ML workloads
AI/ML Engineering: Developing large-scale language models (LLMs) and NLP solutions
Cloud and DevOps: Building efficient data pipelines and deploying large-scale solutions on AWS, Azure, and GCP
Technical Leadership: Leading high-performing teams and driving technical visions&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
