<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on YenKha</title>
    <link>http://localhost:44579/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on YenKha</description>
    <generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright YenKha &amp;copy; {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	    <atom:link href="http://localhost:44579/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://localhost:44579/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:44579/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;transformational-leader-in-ai-ml--backend-platform-engineering&#34;&gt;Transformational Leader in AI, ML &amp;amp; Backend Platform Engineering&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a visionary data and software engineering leader, I drive technical innovation and strategic growth by architecting scalable data platforms, architectures, and pipelines that fuel AI/ML advancements. With expertise in software and backend engineering, I craft efficient, reliable, and future-proof solutions that accelerate AI-powered software product development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the forefront of AI exploration, I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about pushing the boundaries of Large Language Models (LLMs), language understanding, generation, and human-AI collaboration, empowering teams to pioneer groundbreaking AI innovations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;key-expertise&#34;&gt;Key Expertise:&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Architecture: Designing scalable data architectures for AI/ML workloads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Ingestion: Building efficient data pipelines using Apache Spark and Airflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ETL: Developing ETL pipelines using Python, Spark, and SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data Lake: Designing and implementing data lakes using Databricks, Medallion architecture, Azure Blob and Google Cloud Storage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AI &amp;amp; ML: Large Language Models (LLMs), Natural Language Processing (NLP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming &amp;amp; Data: Go, PostgreSQL, Python, Spark, Terraform, Terragrunt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cloud &amp;amp; DevOps: Airflow, AWS, Azure, Datadog, Docker, GCP, Vault, Jfrog Artifactory, Kubernetes, Rancher&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;APIs &amp;amp; Integrations: FastAPI, GraphQL, HuggingFace, Kafka, LLM&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leadership: Technical Leadership, Team Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
